yoursingapore.com 2015-06-11

# Privacy – YourSingapore

##### GENERAL

This is a Singapore Government agency website. We adopt the same principles relating to your privacy as other Government of Singapore websites.  
If you are only browsing this website, we do not capture data that allows us to identify you individually.

If you choose to make an application or send us an e-mail for which you provide us with personally identifiable data, we may share necessary data with other Government agencies, so as to serve you in a most efficient and effective way, unless such sharing is prohibited by law. We will NOT share your personal data with non-Government entities, except where such entities have been authorised to carry out specific Government services. Personal data will only be collected where your consent has been obtained for the collection of the personal data and the purpose for which the personal data will be used.

For your convenience, we may also display to you data you had previously supplied to us or other Government agencies. This will speed up the transaction and save you the trouble of repeating previous submissions. Should the data be out-of-date, please provide us with the latest data. We will retain your personal data only as necessary for the effective delivery of public services to you.

To safeguard your personal data, all electronic storage and transmission of personal data are secured with appropriate security technologies.

This site may contain links to non-Government sites whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these other websites and encourage you to consult the privacy notices of those sites. If you are asked by a non-Government site to link your profile on this website to a non-Government site, or to log in to a non-Government site and link your profile on that site to this website, their content and privacy practices will also apply. 

Please contact [feedback@stb.gov.sg](mailto:feedback@stb.gov.sg): 

  1. For any enquires or feedback on our data protection policies and procedures, 
  2. If you require more information on or access to the data which you have earlier provided to us. 

##### COOKIE POLICY

We use cookie technology to improve and customise your experience on this website, and understand how you are using the website. The cookie technology we use does not capture any personally identifiable data about you but remembers your preferences, such as language and region, which remain as your default settings when you revisit the website.

Some of the cookies we use are session cookies and only last until you close your browser, others are persistent cookies which are stored on your computer for longer. However, the cookies cannot read data off your hard disk.

We may share non-personally identifiable information with third parties so as to provide suggestions to you, personalise content and to enhance your browsing experience on and off our website. These third parties may also collect your non-personally identifiable information when you view or use their applications or websites, and may do this using cookies or other similar technologies. Please review their privacy policies to learn more about the information they collect or receive.

To browse without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. Your experience of this website may be different if you have configured your browser to block cookies as you may not be able to use all interactive features on our sites.
